so let's look at our answer to the uma
smp quiz
we want to have a lot of cores
with this type of architecture so what
are the problems that we'll have to face
the memory will need to be large and
slow and that's because
having more cores
usually means that we will be running
programs that access more data
and we need to keep that data somewhere
so we will need to have a large memory
and that makes the memory slow next that
memory will get too many accesses per
second because the cache misses
from all of the cores will be going to
memory if one of the core generates
cache misses that the memory can survive
doing
two of them it might still survive but
if we have a lot of cores
our memory will probably not be able to
keep up with all of those accesses
we'll need a lot of small memory modules
not necessarily the number of memory
modules in a centralized
memory
doesn't matter what is really needed is
to have enough memory for all the cores
to get enough data in there
and the memory that will keep up with
the bandwidth demands of the course
how many modules we have doesn't really
matter
caches will have very small block size
this is not true either
all of the caches in all of the course
can have
any block size they want the block size
is not divided among the cores
pages for virtual memory become too
small same thing we can have any page
size we want
having more or fewer cores doesn't
affect the page size in virtual memory
so the only options you should have
selected are the first tool